a drone alert has been declared throughout the
объявлена беспилотная опасность по всей
Rostov region, it
территории Ростовской области
is recommended to leave open areas of the
рекомендовано покинуть открытые участки
streets, go indoors and not go near the
улиц зайти в помещение и не подходить к
windows, that is, there is a drone alert in the Rostov region
окнам то есть в Ростовской области
now, it's
сейчас беспилотная
cool, what do you have
опасность прикольно а что у вас
drones, what do you have, what's going on, it's
беспилотники у вас что война идёт
funny, he says, I didn't
прикольно говорит
think you had an air raid alert,
я не думал что у вас в воздушная тревога
hello,
здравствуйте
hi, you're 18,
привет вам есть 18
yes, I understand, I'm from the city of Khmelnitsky, where are you
есть понял я из города Хмельницкий вы
from,
откуда
and I understand, I understand that you're from Russia, from
а я понял я понял что вы из России из
what city did I think you would judge,
какого города я думала вы осудите
that's why it wasn't I understand, I
поэтому было не Я я понимаю я нормально
communicate normally with people, you're just from what city am I
общаюсь с людьми ты просто из какого я
from Yekaterinburg, I'll find out, my father is from
из Екатеринбурга узнаю у меня отец родом
Yekaterinburg, though when it was still
из Екатеринбурга правда когда он ещё в
called Sverdlovsk, yes, I know, and
Свердловском назывался да я знаю а у
my father has the
меня отец у него написано свидетельстве
city of Sverdlovsk written on his birth certificate,
рождения город Свердловск
cool, I understand, you're filming, no, okay, do you
круто понял вы снимаете нет хорошо
want me to film you, no, no, I can
хотите чтобы я вас снял нет не надо могу
film you now, no, I understand, what
сейчас снять не надо понял что вас
brought you to chat roulette, I do
привело в чат рулеточку
n't know, just talk to someone, well,
не знаю просто поговорить с кем-нибудь
I was looking for foreigners to improve my
ну я искала иностранцев чтобы прокачать
language skills, are you improving your language skills somehow?  yes, from a
язык как-то язык прокачиваете да с
foreigner it sounds somehow like I was looking for
иностранца как-то звучит как-то искал
foreigners to improve my
иностранцев чтобы прокачать язык
English language well look English and
английски ну смотрите английский а
English I understand
английский понял
yes here in Ukraine English is a
да у нас просто в Украине английский -
language called English language and
это мова называется английская мова а
language is to
язык - это
improve yes improve language but with
прокачатьк да прокачать язык но с
foreigners it is somehow not
иностранцами оно как-то не так
perceived well well I
воспринимается
understand well and what do you think why Russia is at war
понял а как вы считаете почему воюет
with Ukraine
Россия с Украиной
I don’t know and do
я не знаю
you have someone you know who is at war
а у вас есть кто-то знакомый кто воюет
no
нет
and what do you think about this Ukraine in
а как относитесь к этой Украине в
childhood
детстве
up to what age my aunt and I and my
до какого года у меня и тёт у меня и
aunt are from there no I was about four years old
тётя оттуда нет мне было годика четыре
so I understand Ukrainian a little that is well
вот я понимаю украинский чуть-чуть то
I lived there for 2 years up to six years
есть ну я жила там 2 года лет до шести
well and then my father died and I
ну а потом у меня отец умер и я
moved to Russia my
переехала в Россию
mother is Russian yes
мама русская да
no and
нет
that we moved to Russia I do
а что в Россию переехали
n’t know my father decided so well how can I say
не знаю отец решил так ну как сказать
so my father died so no before that my father
так отец умер так нет до этого отец
wanted us to move here we were already
хотел чтобы мы сюда переехали мы уже
getting ready to move and my father at that
собирались переезжать и отец под это
time well that is he died and in what
время ну то есть умер а са в какой
region did we live my
области жили
mother said something about Kharkov I understand that’s
мама что-то говорила про Харьков понял
where we lived and how are you how are you  now
вот там жили а как ты как ты сейчас
you relate to the fact that Russia is bombing
относишься к тому что Россия бомбит
Kharkov I
Харьков
don’t know mm I don’t participate like I don’t listen to the
не знаю мм я не участвую типа не слушаю
news like I don’t sit like no well
как бы новости не сижу типа
anyway somewhere I know things
не ну всё равно же где-то знаю дела
look I love both countries like I don’t
смотрите я люблю обе страны типа я не
want them to fight so that there is a
хочу чтобы они воевали чтобы было
truce that is and who is to blame that they are
перемирие то есть а кто виноват что они
fighting I don’t
воюют
know I don’t understand this I don’t
я не знаю я не разбираюсь в этом я не
know history understand that is you are an expert
знаю историю поня то есть ты специалист
only in pumping up the language yes well so
только по прокачиванию языка да
on A with how many foreigners have you already
по А со сколькими иностранцами ты уже
pumped up the language
прокачивала язык
no I just like talked like that
нет я просто типа разговаривала так
new words there learned what is that
новые слова там подучивала что
with Koreans I communicated in English
такое вот то с корейцами на английском
then just with people from well other
общалась то просто с людьми из ну других
countries that is also in English well yes
стран то есть тоже на английском ну да
come on so uh
давай так
how many foreigners have you already had with
э-э сколько иностранцев было у тебя уже
whom you pumped up your language
таких с которыми ты прокачивала язык
I don’t know I haven’t read well
свой я не знаю я не читала ну
approximately
приблизительно
well 4-5 people somewhere like that well your
ну человек 4-5 где-то так ну у тебя
language is not pumped up enough if there are
довольно непрокачанный язык если их
four or five of them well yes and you need to
четыре-пять ну да а надо больше язык
pump up the language more recently a friend just downloaded me and
прокачивать недавно скачала мне просто
told me that like she was
подруга рассказала то что типа тут
sitting here talking like and a friend is an
сидела тут общалась типа а подруга
expert in  pumping up the tongue with
специалист в накачивании языка с
foreigners yes I don't know she just
иностранцами да я не знаю просто она
told me and that's it and you only
рассказывала и всё а ты только язык
pump up the tongue or do you pump up your lips and cheeks too with
качаешь или там губы щёки тоже качаешься
foreigners
иностранцами
no
нет
just with just the tongue the muscles will get tired you
просто с одним языком будут мышцы
need to like
уставать нужно типа чтобы
work all the muscles that participate in
работали все мышцы которые участвуют в
this
этом
process with foreigners
процессе с иностранцами
you definitely don't film it definitely don't film it
вы точно не снимаете точно не снимаю у
you had such a face like how do you
тебя такое лицо было такое что как
know a computer error there well so well
знаешь компьютерная ошибка эррор там
you just have a T-shirt and you are
ну так ну просто у вас и футболка и вы
on a chair I thought you are filming on a chair
на стуле я подумала вы снимаете на стуле
I am always on this chair we
я всегда на этом стуле мы вопросы
asked questions about politics but I don't understand well
задавали про политику но я не разбираюсь
I am just interested in the idea that I don't
ну мне просто интересно идея в том что я
understand either but yes but
тоже не разбираюсь но да но на мой город
Russian bombs are flying at my city and that's why I want to
летят российские бомбы и я поэтому хочу
figure it out that's why I am asking Russians well
разобраться поэтому и спрашиваю россиян
you could have read the news it
ну вы же могли новости почитать там же
should have been written like that and you could have
должно быть написано так и вы же могли
read the news but you didn't read I read and I did
новости почитать но вы не почитали читаю
n't read either I decided to come out here and
и я не читал я тоже я решил сюда выйти
ask the Russians directly
спросить напрямую у россиян
and there was a desire that well that's how you
а было желание что вот ну вот как вы
pumped up the tongue with some foreigner there
прокачивали язык с каким-то иностранцем
was a desire to somehow pump up the tongue with him well
было желание как-то прокачать с ним язык
not through chat roulette but in person
ну не через чат рулетку а вживую
[music]
[музыка]
no well they we are from different countries how to
нет ну они мы из разных стран как с ними
meet them that is well
встретиться то есть
if for example look a person
ну если там например вот смотри человек
from Korea wants to pump up his language and you
из Кореи хочет прокачать свой язык и ты
want to pump up your language and you
хочешь прокачать свой язык да и вы
will meet yes on neutral territory
встретитесь да на нейтральной территории
and you will pump up each other's language
и будете прокачивать язык друг другу
mm no I didn't think about it
мм нет я об этом не думала
somehow they say that with close contact the
как-то говорят что при близком контакте
language is pumped up better well I don't
лучше язык прокачивается
know there
ну не знаю
were no such thoughts
не было такого типа мыслей
understood
понял
listen but
слушай а
what about the percentages what and I have
вот проценты что-что а у меня процентов
little percentages I have
мало у меня
5% and the phone is charging then yes then
5% и телефон на зарядке тогда да тогда
quickly-quickly yes I will say listen but
быстро-быстро да я скажу слушай а вот
look what-what I have everything I looked yes everything is
смотри что-что я всё я посмотрела да всё
fine yes on charging listen but it
нормально да на зарядке слушай а вот
turns out when Russia attacked
получается когда Россия напала на
Ukraine there were Russian soldiers of
Украину тут же российские военные
Ukrainian girls how do you feel about this
украинских девушек как ты к этому
mm I don't know like I don't know who is on whom and
мм не знаю типа я не знаю кто на кого и
how what is happening on I am
как происходит то что на
not aware of all this are you really
Я не в курсе этого всего ты реально
why or are you pretending
почему или ты притворяешься
no well you first look the first feeling
нет ну ты пер смотри первое ощущение
was yes that you seem to be such an educated
было да что ты вроде такая образованная
girl and then just some you know
девушка да потом просто какой-то знаешь
a piece like well there right then like I'm
скусток вроде ну там прям да потом вроде
trying to talk well not really
пробую говорить ну не совсем
well here in general you I don't understand how
ну ну тут вообще ты я не понимаю как
you really are 18
тебе реально есть 18
yes how did you live to such an age with
есть как ты до такого возраста дожила с
the absence of how can you live like that
отсутствием как можно жить такой типа да
and tell me there I don't know there what
и говорить мне ещё там я не знаю там что
about I didn't know you really you just
про я не знал ты реально ты просто
know that imagine yes that
знаешь что вот представь да что тебя
Kadyrov's men come to you and you in short and
придут кадыровцы да и тебе короче и
forward in short and for you it will be normal
вперёд короче и тебе это будет нормально
bad no it's bad bad and when when
плохо нет это плохо плохо а когда когда
they are in Ukraine uh girls is it normal
они в Украине ээ девушек это нормально
for you or you don't understand it no
для тебя или ты это не разбираешь нет
it's bad I haven't heard about
это плохо я не слышала про
it well I'm saying that it's very bad to
это ну говорю что это очень плохо так
act like that at all it's impossible that is
поступать вообще нельзя то есть
Russian military agree
российские военные согласна
m no that is if there are people who
м нет то есть если есть люди которые так
act like that it's bad just whether I understood everything I understood understood
поступают это плохо просто ли всё понял
everything let's not talk about
я понял понял всё понял давай не будем о
politics about war understood everything with you like with a
политике о войне понял всё с тобой как с
Barbie doll is needed listen how much do
куклой Барби нужна слушай сколько вот
you think how much a guy should
как ты считаешь сколько должен парень
get a salary for you to date him
получать зарплаты чтобы ты с ним
well it doesn't really matter well
ну неважно особо
and if so in order to have a family well
ну а если так чтобы чтобы семью ж ну
family children you need to somehow so that he
семья ж дети нужно как-то чтобы он
earns how much well like more from  I
зарабатывал сколько ну типа ещё от
can split it in half sometimes pay
пополам могу поделить иногда заплатить
for myself that is, it's not really about the
за себя то есть дело особо-таки не в
money you could say
деньгах можно сказать
but also about what the person is like and that
а ещё свя то что какой сам человек и то
is, if he needs something I'll help in
есть если ему что-то нужно я помогу в
any situation like if he has problems I'll
любой ситуации типа если у него проблемы
help too
тоже помогу
but so that the guy is ready to
ну а чтобы вот парень был готов к
get married by the wedding how much should he
женитьбе к свадьбе сколько он должен
get
получать
mm I don't know I don't have any special criteria
мм не знаю у меня нет особых критерий
for this that is he may not work at all yes
насчёт этого то есть он может вообще не
no that he doesn't work no that
работать да нет то что не работает нет
is he can get 5,000 rubles
то есть он может получать 5.000 руб
total yes per month well
всего да в месяц
that's not much somehow well like that's that's that's how much is not a little that's
ну это мало как-то ну типа вот вот вот
how much
вот то сколько немало это сколько
I don't know
я не знаю
if he will get 10,000 rubles per month
если он 10.000 руб будет в месяц
normally well
получать нормально
if he's a teenager like or at the
ну если он подросток типа или там в
university what teenager well if the wedding is
универе какой подросток ну если свадьба
already supposed to be then yes that means I do
уже должна быть то да значит
n't know he won't be able to like a wedding even
не знаю он не сможет типа свадьба даже
like
типа
I don't want that at all yes come on come on in
я не хочу такое вообще да давай давай
short I understood at 10,000 10,000 rubles a
короче я понял в 10.000 10.000 руб в
month not ready for a wedding 20,000 rubles a
месяц не готов к свадьбе 20.000 руб в
month I do
месяц
n't know what kind of wedding it will be for  20,000
не знаю что за свадьба будет за 20.000
if he's like if we chip in
если он типа если мы скинемся
then how much does a guy need to earn in Russia
то сколько нужно получать парню в России
so that he can get married
да чтобы уже можно было жениться
I don't care it doesn't matter
мне неважно неважно
yes everyone who says it doesn't matter everything everything
да все кто говорят неважно все все
because if it doesn't matter yes a guy may
потому что если неважно да парень может
not work at all yes sit in short
вообще не работать да сидеть короче
watch football on the couch and drink beer
смотреть футбол на диване и пиво пить
then it's still important yes hello to
значит всё-таки важно да здравствуйте
you heart
вам сердечко
where are my thank you
вообще где мои спасибо
and this is it 100
а вот это он 100
daddy show me show
папочка покажи покажи
this I'm fine let's talk
этого я всё нормально давайте поговорим
to your
с вашим
husband then I'm
мужем потом
sorry please what happened to him they
Извините пожалуйста что с ним случилось
don't take him to war here's what
на войну не берут вот тепать вот
he came back from the war what he came back from the war
что он он с войны вернулся
no I was a nazi as a child
нет я в детстве нац
and what does he want to do to war well show
а что он хочет на войну
me this to my face you can
а ну покажи ты мне в глаза это сможешь
say it will you have the strength to say it to my face
сказать будет сила у тебя сказать в
or are you hiding behind a woman
глаза или ты за женщину прячешься
come on show me to my face tell me
давай покажи мне в глаза мне скажи
I'm with a woman come on come on come on come on she had a
я с женщиной поду давай давай давай
squirrel
давай давай давай давай у неё белка
drink it it's
выпил
not entirely clear what you
не совсем понятно что вы мне
're showing me I don't
демонстрируете ничего особенного не
see anything special well you don't see and I didn't understand anything
вижу а ну ви не вид понял а я ничего не
I
Я
just went away and  I left I understood yes
просто отлучилась а отлучилось понял да
I thought you were showing me this
я думал вы это показывайте мне
and I think what will I see there that I haven't
и думаю что там я такое увижу что не
seen again again you're here and where are the earlobes
видел опять опять ты здесь а где мочки
went from here I'm talking to a woman yes where did you go from
пошёл отсюда я с женщиной говорю
here
да онде отсюда пошёл
what's wrong with him you knocked him out
что с ним такое ты его вырубила
yes there he sits so everything is quiet already fell silent yes you to him he's
да вот он сидит так всё тихо уже
all stalled
замолчал да ты ему он всё заглох
he wants such a song so that he gets quietly I sing to
он хочет такую песню чтобы получил тихо
myself the edge
я пою я себя краю
fell night
опустилась ночь
like mom sang him a lullaby yes oh come on
как мама колыбельную ему пела да а ну
pv
давай пв
damn you're pretty you have a heart you have a
блин ты симпатичная тебе сердечко у тебя
very kind soul
очень добрая душа
man you really are but you're a beauty well so oh
мужик у тебя правда но ты красавица
and I know that I'm a beauty yes you're great you have a
ой а я знаю что я краса да ты молодец у
big soul I see your
тебя у тебя душа большая я вижу твой
this rich inner world eyes are
этот богатый внутренний мир глаза
shining right smile cool
светятся прямо ж улыбка клас
I don't understand and about such and such you know about such and
я не понимаю а про такихто знаешь про
such good became in short you're a Jew I do
такихто хороший стал короче ты еврей я
n't I don't understand why Why do you need a Jew
не я не понимаю зачем Зачем тебе еврей
why do you need such a cool girl like that Why do you need this
зачем тебе такой классной девушке такой
she's a Jew so I sing a song boys both
она еврейка так я пою песню мальчики оба
from this and the other side I sing you a song
с той и с другой стороны я пою вам песню
let's
давайте
mine asked to
мой просил
meet from Israel Israel
постречается из Израиля израиля
quietly edge quietly edge  tadada ...
тихо краю тихо краю
Nadya
ростов прикольно а чём общаешься Надюха
what about what Nadya are you talking about
что о чём Надя общаешься
here or here at all
тут или вообще тут вообще
here at all Yes yes just
тут вообще Да да просто
what the hell yes I asked yes what do you
а что блин да я попросила а да что тебе
love you such a nice baby yeah
сердечко ты такая приятная малышка
listen and where are you from I'm from the
угу слушай а а ты ты откуда я сам из
city of
города
Khmelnitsky you just feel
Хмельницкий у тебя прямо аж ощущается
so feminine listen did
женственность такая слушай а у тебя
anyone you know die in the war
кто-то из знакомых погиб на войне
yeah who's
да кто
my uncle died my ex stepfather
у меня дядя умер у меня бывший отчем
and how did he get to the war well he
а как он на войну попал
signed a contract and went to SW and
ну подписал контракт и поехал на SW а
why did he sign it he
зачем подписал
wanted money understood what do you think he did
денег захотел понял как ты считаешь он
or not did
или нет
he
он
understand
что понял
yeah what do
угу
you think why is Russia fighting with
как ты считаешь зачем Россия воюет с
Ukraine
Украиной
fighting yeah
воюет да
how do I know well what do
я откуда знаю
you think I do
ну ты как думаешь
n't
не
know I just got a message
знаю во мне только что сообщение пришло
what
какое
there nothing is visible tell me that in that
там ничего не видно скажи что в том
message nothing is visible
сообщении не видно ничего
baby can you read there you can't see a
малышка можешь прочитать там не видно
drone danger has been declared throughout the
объявлена беспилотная опасность по всей
Rostov region it
территории Ростовской области
is recommended to leave open areas of the
рекомендовано покинуть открытые участки
streets go indoors and not go near the
улиц зайти в помещение и не подходить к
windows that is in the Rostov region
окнам то есть в Ростовской области
now there is a drone danger
сейчас беспилотная опасность
cool what do you have drones do you have a
прикольно а что у вас беспилотники у вас
war going on  he says it funny
что война идёт прикольно говорит
i didn't think that you had an air raid alarm in Rostov
я не думал что у вас в Росто воздушная
he sends it every day
он каждый день
then somewhere at 6:00 in the morning they
присылают потом где-то в 6:00 утра
write: "All clear for drone danger
пишут: "Отбой беспилотной опасности по
throughout the Rostov region" and
всей территории Ростовской области" а
what happens to you it flies in and goes boom well where
что у вас бывает прилетает бабахает
I live like there's nothing I
ну там где я живу типа ничего нету
understood and so the news what do you think is the reason for the
понял а так новости как считаешь из-за
drone danger in your Rostov region
беспилотная опасность
because drones are flying from Ukraine and who is to
потому что дроны с Украины летают а кто
blame for the drones flying from Ukraine
виноват в том что дроны с Украины летают
yes how do I know why you ask me such
да я откуда знаю ты что мне такие
questions I am asking you what Putin
вопросы задаёшь я тебе что Путин
Volodka or what not well what do you think you are a
Володька что ли не ну ты как думаешь ты
simple girl I am a simple guy
же простая девушка я простой парень
I don't have enough to send TikToks can you
я не хватит тиктоки отправлять ты можешь
show them to me we are
мне их показывать мы рядом
sitting next to each other let's have a normal chat
сидим давай нормально пообщаемся
let's yes that's what you think who is to blame for the
давай да вот как ты считаешь кто виноват
drones flying to your
в том что летят беспилотники на вашу
Rostov region
Ростовскую область
Zelensky Zelensky
зеленский зеленский
Zelensky that is you Nadya from Rostov you
зеленский то есть ты Надя из Ростова
think that Zelensky is to blame for the
считаешь что Зеленский виноват в том что
drones flying in your region yes and why is
у вас летают беспилотники да а почему
Zelensky to blame how  you think so and what does it have to do with it well
Зеленский виноват как ты думаешь
like I don't understand
так а при чём тут ну типа я не понимаю
here you were living and Zelensky launched
вот вы себе жили жили и Зеленский взял
a drone at you I
запустил на вас беспилотник
heard that there was some dispute there
слышала то что там что-то не поделили
in short they divided
короче подели
uh Ukraine was somehow connected with
ээ Украина была связана как-то на
Zelensky with Trump
Зеленске с Трампом
then all sorts of things happened Trump refused to
потом всякая произошла трамп отказался
help him why did all this start I don't
помогать из-за чего это всё началось я
know anything
доси не знаю
there everything they say in the news everything they
там всё что говорят в новостях всё что
say on the Internet these are all just
говорят в интернете это всё просто
different things and in fact the truth
разные вещи и на самом деле правду мне
seems to me no one knows
кажется никто не знает
who is to blame what is to blame I don't
кто виноват что виноват я не
know of course for my homeland I won't
знаю я конечно же за свою родину я не
say what I don't care
буду говорить то что мне там да плевать
I'm on the neutral side no like I have my
я на нейтральной стороне нет типа у меня
own homeland I'm for
родина своя я за
it I won't blame my own and why is
неё я не буду обвинять своих а почему
your homeland killing people in another
твоя родина убивает людей в другой
homeland
родине
and why is that homeland killing our homeland
а почему та родина убивает нашу родину
well our homeland is defending itself everything is
ну наша родина защищается всё
simple every homeland is also defending itself well your homeland is
просто каждая родина тоже защищается ну
not your homeland is not defending itself your homeland
ваша родина не ваша родина не защищается
attacked that is our homeland you are ugly well you
ваша родина напала то есть у нас родина
speak as if we know we
ну ты так говоришь как будто мы знаем мы
know nothing his homeland is our ugly
ничего не знаем его родина наша уродина
imagine
прикинь
yeah  you and who are
да ты ещё и
you studying to be, baby
А ты на кого учишься малышка
whose Crimea
чей Крым
who are you studying to be
на кого учишься
whose Crimea let's have a normal conversation and
чей Крым давай нормально пообщаемся а
what about a second
что секунду
again a little bit something
опять чуть-чуть сейчас что-то будет
creepy is going to happen
стрёмное
let's ask you a question Nadyukha will now
давай тебе такой вопрос надюха сейчас
blow everyone up glory to whom
разнесёт всех слава кому
glory to the CPSU that's how it was written in the
слава КПСС тоже так было написано в
Soviet Union
Советском Союзе
I just have a question for you glory to Russia or
я тебе просто вопрос слава России или
glory to Ukraine glory to Styko
слава Украины слава Стыко
two choices glory to Russia glory to
два выбора слава России слава Украине ну
Ukraine well of course glory to Ukraine Russia has no
конечно слава Украине у России нету
glory as part of Russia and what about Dzirukha and in
славы в составе России а в чём Джируха а
general she went and
вообще пошла паспорт
took her passport that was the bomb like
взяла вот это бомба была капец лайк
pitpokoman hello hi
питпокоман здравствуйте
let's have a normal conversation I'm from
привет давайте нормально пообщаемся я из
Ukraine where are you from
Украины вы откуда
excuse me
извините
what city are you from where are you from I'm from the
с какого вы города
city of Khmelnitsky where are you from this
вы откуда я из города Хмельницкий вы
Ukraine yes this is Ukraine and where are you from I'm
это Украина да это Украина а вы откуда
from Russia
я из России
I can see from your face what city what as
я вижу по лицу город какой
you can see I can see from your face that
что как вы видите я вижу по лицу что
Russia is not China not America like but what city I can
Россия не Китай не Америка типа а город
tell from my face that I'm from Russia well yes a
у меня по лицу видно что я из России ну
Russian face a woman is Russian
да русское лицо женщина русская
Russian yes
русская да
again a Russian woman is neither Chinese nor
ещё раз русская женщина ни китаянка ни
Ukrainian nor German  not a
украинка ни немка ни
Finn from what city are we
финка из какого города
mistaken comrade at the beginning well come on
ошибаемся товарищ в начале а ну давай
surprise me well come on
удиви меня
again well will
ну давай ещё раз
we surprise each other or you me
ну удивлять будем мы друг друга или вы
come on you tell me what city are you from
давайте вы мне скажите с какого вы
and why should I tell you what
а зачем я буду вам говорить с какого я
city I am from well let's chat
город ну давайте пообщаемся
well we haven't even met you
ну мы же с вами даже не познакомились вы
right away And what city are you from my
сразу же А из какого ты города меня
name is Andrey from the city of Khmelnitsky what is your
зовут Андрей из города Хмельницкий тебя
name from what city are you from the
как зовут из какого ты города
city of Kursk
город Курск
damn they don't
блин вас там не
bomb you there I say they don't bomb you there
бомбят говорю вас там не бомбят
and what do you think I think they
а ты как думаешь думаю
bomb poor things do
бомбят бедняшки
n't you feel sorry for
тебе не жалко
Kursk honestly tell me
курск честно сказать
how
говори как я
happy I am because I remember how Kursk
радуюсь потому что я помню как Курск
rejoiced when they bombed Ukraine
радовался когда бомбили Украину
well you see retribution comes when it's
ну видишь приходит возмездие
all over what will you be
когда всё закончится чему ты будешь
happy about it will end
радоваться это закончится
yes with the burning of the Kremlin
да с сожжением Кремля
some Kremlin in Moscow Moscow yes
кремля какого в Москве московского да
for some reason And do you still have in the Kursk
почему-то А у вас есть ещё в Курский
Kremlin
Кремль
no for some reason I think that it seems to me it
нет я почему-то думаю что мне кажется
seems to me it's impossible well
это мне кажется это невозможно ну вот
once it seemed impossible that the
когда-то было казалось невозможно что
Ukrainians would capture Sudzha really
украинцы Суджу захватят правда
I don't want to I'm not interested in the whole
я не хочу мне не интересна именно вся
situation that is connected with the
ситуация которая связана с
military operation now
сейчас военной операцией
ok let's have a normal conversation look what do
хорошо давай нормально пообщаемся смотри
you think I'm not arguing about the
вот как ты считаешь я не ссорюсь про
military operation but I just have an interesting
военную операцию но просто интересное
opinion do you have someone from If you're
мнение у тебя кто-то из Если ты меня
going to film me now I won't
сейчас будешь снимать на видео я не буду
talk I won't I'm not filming
говорить не буду я не снимаю на видео
no you're filming I'm just
нет ты снимаешь не снимаю я просто
talking I'm an ordinary person I
общаюсь я обычный человек я после работы
talk to Russians after work because I'm not a politician that's
общаюсь с россиянами потому что я не
why you have 100-500
политик поэтому у тебя 100- 500 тут
stars here and I understand that stop stop I
звёздочек и я понимаю это стоп стоп я
work I work as a teacher at the
работаю я работаю преподавателем в
European University that's why I have the
Европейском университете поэтому у меня
flag of the
флаг
European Union I give lectures well
евросоюза я лекции провожу
damn you can give lectures uh for
ну блин ты можешь лекции проводить э для
students and leave it there that's right
учеников и оставить это там правильно
when you communicate with real people
вот ты когда с с живыми людьми общаешься
it's always here yes it's always
он у меня всегда тут да он у меня всегда
hanging here I can't film it it's
висит тут я же его не могу снимать он
big move your
большой
hand again it's a
руку ещё раз проведи
big flag it's hanging big how
это большой он флаг он висит большой как
can I believe you that you're
я могу тебе поверить что ты меня сейчас
not writing me now damn I give you my word as a boy my
не пишешь блин даю тебе слово пацана
word yes damn my word as a boy you know that come on you
слово да блин слово пацана это знаешь
need to what series did you watch no I didn't
давай надо что сериал смотрел нет не
watch by the way I didn't have time
смотрел кстати не было времени
what watch  cool I'm 43 years old
а что посмотри прикольно мне 43 года
you how old are you a
тебе сколько
little over twenty over
чуть больше двадцати
twenty young
больше двадцати молоденькая
still like pink
ещё любишь розовый цвет
why is everything so pink there are
почему ну всё такое розовенькое там
seedlings in the back and
там рассада
that's a phytolamp I
а это фитолампа
understand I think this is an atmosphere lamp this is a
понял я думаю это атмосферка такая это
phytolamp for this is for seedlings it shines
фитолампа для это для рассады светит
cunningly-cunningly here I was thinking VIP Instagram
хитро-хитро тут думал VIP Instagram
webcam and here Yes seedlings
вебкам а тут Да рассада
and what about tomatoes
а что там помидоры
yes what varieties are
а да какие сорта
there under the windows I have
там подоконнечные у меня
three coming out to the garden one
три выходцы в огород один
[music]
[музыка]
and yellow this oh my
и жёлтый этот
God watermelon
господи арбуз
cool Caesar
прикольно цезарь
interesting this is a yellow tomato Yes I don't have
интересно это жёлтый помидор да
cherry yellow No cherry I have
у меня нет черри жёл Нет черри у меня
red orange and purple-black
красные оранжевые и фиолетово-чёрные
cool and you yourself do you have a husband
прикольно а ты сама же у тебя есть муж
brother some kind of relatives one
брат какой-то там родственники
of them is at war
кто-то из них на войне
I don't have no
у меня нет
can't have everyone has someone
да не может быть у каждого есть кто-то
at war
на войне
I I don't have anyone
я У меня никого нет
understand what do you do baby
понял а кем работаешь малышка
I work as a cashier where in the store
я работаю касиром где в магазине
in Pyaterochka
в Пятёрочке
why right away in Pyaterochka well I
почему сразу в Пятёрочке
don't know
ну не знаю
who it's
кем
stuck so let's go let's go further
зависло так поехали поехали дальше
subscribe to my Telegram directly immediately
подпишись на мій Telegram прямо зараз
axis vin and popik
ось він а попик
ce even more and more importantly youtube is pushing
це дуже і дуже важливо youtube заганяє
us through kargers into a shadow ban and the
нас через каргерки в тіньовий бан и дуже
video is no longer shown to people,
багато відео не показуется людям вчасно
information about the stream is not shown at all times
не показуется інформація про стрими тому
in order for us to have short-term communication
для того щоб ми мали оперативный зв'язок
subscribe directly immediately and the pop there in the
підпишиться прямо зараз а попик там в
telegram okmdeo is also tsikava and
телеграме окмдео ще теж є цікава и
useful information and we are responsible for you to
корисна информация и мы повинні з вами
trimate a permanent operational connection
тримати постійний оперативный зв'язок
regardless of the fact that we will show you about this
незалежно від того чи покаже вам про це
YouTube glory to Ukraine subscribe
YouTube слава Украине підпишись